RG 097, Connecticut Commission on the Arts
Connecticut State Library
- Series 6. Educational Records, 1967-1976
  - Education Program, General, 1966 - 1975 (Box 36)
    - N.E.A. Poets in the Colleges Program (Box 36)
    - N.E.A. Artist in Residence Program, 1970-1973 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. Information, Descriptive Booklet, 1971 (Box 36)
    - Education Budget FY, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - North Haven High School, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Chanti High School (Box 36)
    - Bingham Elementary School, V.A.P., 1972 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. Year End Report, 8/69, 1968-1969 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P., A Personal Account, 1969-1970 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. Summaries, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. Year End Report, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - A.I.R. Year End Report, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - Poets Year End Report, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - Bingham Elementary School, Student Evaluation and Teacher Comments, 1972 (Box 36)
    - Education Budget, FY, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P., Hartford, C.R.E.C., 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. Hooker School, 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. L.E.A.R.N., 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P., Progress Report, 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P., New Haven, A.C.E.S., 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. at R.E.S.C.U.E., 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - Poet/ Student Teaching Programs, CCSC-Newington High School, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Whittier Evaluation, 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P., Windsor L.P. Wilson, Jr. High, 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P., General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P., Poetry, Northwest, 1969-1970 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P., R.E.S.C.U.E., 1969-1970 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. Procedures, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
    - V.A.P.’s East Hampton, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
    - V.A.P., New Haven, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
    - V.A.P., C.R.E.C., 1969-1971 (Box 37)
    - Educational Research Associates, 1971 (Box 37)
    - V.A.P.’s, 1970-1971 (Box 37)
    - Barnard Brown Elementary School, Hartford, 1970-1971 (Box 37)
    - Bloomfield Jr. High And High School, 1970-1971 (Box 37)
    - New Haven Arts Council (Box 37)
    - Northwest Poetry Project, 1970-1971 (Box 37)
    - NEA Application, Choate and A.I.R., 1972-1973 (Box 37)
    - Poets in the Colleges, Evaluation Report, 1972-1973 (Box 37)
    - State Arts Councils Testimony, Washington, 1970 (Box 37)
    - Summer Arts Recreation Program, Hartford, 1971 (Box 37)
    - V.A.P. Report, 1968-1969 (Box 37)
    - V.A.P. Evaluation Memo, V. Miller, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
    - V.A.P. Bridgeport, Groton, Waterbury, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
    - V.A.P. North Haven High School, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
    - V.A.P. East Hampton, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
    - Alliance for the Arts Education and N.E.A., A.I.S. (Box 37)
    - A.I.S. Study Committee, N.A.S.A.A. (Box 37)
    - Kathy Klein, A.I.S. Film Video (Box 37)
    - A.I.R. Dance Component (Box 37)
    - A.I.R. Evaluation, 1972-1973 (Box 37)
    - A.I.R. Film, Cheshire, Shanti, Choate, Spr., 1973 (Box 37)
    - N.E.A. New England Regional Meeting (Box 37)
    - 19th, V.A.P., 1972-1973 (Box 37)
    - Guideline to Education Program, 1977-1978 (Box 37)
    - Education Guidelines, 1976-1977 (Box 37)
    - Outreach to Boards of Education and Schools (Box 37)
    - Education Hearing, 1971 April 6 (Box 37)
    - V.A.P. - Final Report, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
    - Master Poet Project, Minnesota (Box 37)
    - V.A.P., 1969-1970 (Box 37)
    - Metro, C.R.E.C. contracts, 1970 (Box 37)
    - Create Evaluation, Robbins, 1970 (Box 37)
    - C.C.A. Annual Report (Box 37)
    - Education in the Endowment (Box 37)
    - Education Program Data (Box 37)
    - Dean Lichtman, August ’76 N.E.A., Artist Evaluation, 1976 (Box 37)
    - Program Data, 1976-1977 (Box 37)
    - T.R.A.P., 1976-1977 (Box 37)
    - T.R.A.P., 1974-1975 (Box 37)
    - Program Data, 1974-1976 (Box 37)
    - Education Planning, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
    - Education Programs, Miscellaneous Information, 1973-1974 (Box 37)
    - Artists’ Registry (Box 37)
    - A.I.R. Report, 1970-1971 (Box 37)
    - Connecticut Comm. Arts Appropriation Request, 1970 (Box 37)
    - C.C.A. Budget Request, 1971 (Box 37)
    - C.C.A., Report, 1965 (Box 37)
    - Create Literature (Box 37)
    - General Information, A.I.R. (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous Letters (Box 37)
    - T.R.A.P. Special Project Grants, 1973-1974 (Box 38)
    - T.R.A.P., 1974-1975 (Box 38)
    - T.R.A.P. Evaluation, 1974-1975 (Box 38)
    - T.R.A.P., 1975-1976 (Box 38)
    - T.R.A.P., 1976-1977 (Box 38)
    - Education Program, 1973-1974 (Box 38)
    - Education Program, 1974-1975 (Box 38)
    - Education Program, Lists, Statistics, etc, 1975-1976 (Box 38)
    - Commission Correspondence (Box 38)
    - Various Address Lists (Box 38)
    - Convent of the Sacred Hearts (letters) (Box 38)
    - Marion G. Anderson (Box 38)
    - The Book About Animals (Box 38)
    - Louis C. Cormier (Box 38)
    - Circulation Correspondence, Education (Box 38)
    - Jacqueline Eagels (Box 38)
    - Jacqueline Daffner (Box 38)
    - Mary A Gild (Box 38)
    - Corrine T. Dixon (Box 38)
    - Gayle P. Edmonds (Box 38)
    - Doris Fredericks (Box 38)
    - Dorothy R. Gilliam (Box 38)
    - Merilyn Hardy (Box 38)
    - Ann Heckman (Box 38)
    - Ruth C. Jarvis (Box 38)
    - T.R.A.P. Agreed Funded, 1975-1976 (Box 38)
    - Charlotte Winslow (Box 38)
    - David Watson (Box 38)
    - Richard Von Hooran (Box 38)
    - Patricia Prindibille (Box 38)
    - Phyllis A. Pliska (Box 38)
    - Roger Newbury (Box 38)
    - Carol Mazzorana (Box 38)
    - Nora Luena (Box 38)
    - Betty LaPoint (Box 38)
    - Raymond Kojak (Box 38)
    - T.R.A.P. Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 38)
    - T.R.A.P. Official File, 1975-1976 (Box 38)
    - Contact Progress (Box 38)
    - Education, Financial Information - Connecticut State Dept. of Education (Box 38)
    - Completed Information Sheets (Box 38)
    - Contracts and Grants Number System, 1973-1974 (Box 38)
    - Correspondence,- 32, 1976-1979 (Box 39)
    - Meetings of Educational Organizations, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
    - Private Schools (Box 39)
    - Arts in Special Education (Box 39)
    - Vocational Training - Arts (Box 39)
    - Educational Journal - Miscellaneous (Box 39)
    - Mailing Record - Poets in the Schools (Box 39)
    - Responses to Ed. Books (Box 39)
    - Reactions to Poets-in-Schools (Box 39)
    - Orff Programs - Connecticut Music (Box 39)
    - Music Education - people, etc. (Box 39)
    - Connecticut Alliance for Arts Education, Connecticut, State Dept. of Education (Box 39)
    - New London Project - Claire Dale (Box 39)
    - J.D.R. 3rd / C.C.A. relationship (Box 39)
    - J.D.R. 3rd/New York City Project (Box 39)
    - Special Education Resource Center (S.E.R.C.) (Box 39)
    - San Francisco Arts (Box 39)
    - SPRED -Regional Arts H.S. (Box 39)
    - School Volunteer Association, Bridgeport (Box 39)
    - HEW-OE Arts Education Grant Program, 1975 June 20 (Box 39)
    - Environmental Awareness (Title III) (Box 39)
    - Alliance for Arts Education (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Memo’s, letters (Box 39)
    - A.I.S. - Writer-Photographer Grant, Applications and references (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence - S.R.S., 1973-1974 (Box 39)
    - Poets Program Letters (Box 39)
    - Principal’s Letter (Box 39)
    - Emergency School Aid Funds - Title VII, 1975 (Box 39)
    - ARTSJOBS Title X (Box 39)
    - Education Staff Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 39)
    - Title X Dept. of Commerce to N.E.A. to Conn. U.R.I. (Box 39)
    - Artist/Administrator Conference, 1975 (Box 39)
    - T.R.A.P.’s, 1974-1975 (Box 39)
    - Teacher Training (Box 39)
    - Teachers Centers (Box 39)
    - Teacher Certification (Box 39)
  - Title III Elementary and Secondary Education Act (ESEA) Advisory Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 59)
    - Title III (Box 59)
    - Talcott Mountain Science Center, On Site Evaluation (Box 59)
    - Project Discuss, On Site Evaluation (Box 59)
    - Project Metro, On Site Evaluation (Box 59)
    - Project SPRED, On Site Evaluation (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous Material (Box 59)
- Series 7. Music, 1973-1977
  - New England Contemporary Music Circuit, 1973-1975 (Box 40)
    - Poster Design (Box 40)
    - Nowak Evaluation, 1975-1976 (Box 40)
    - Budget, Payment, Fin. Report, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Forms, Sponsor List, Calen. Of Events (Box 40)
    - New England Contemporary Ensemble (Box 40)
    - Mass. Council on Arts & Humanities (Box 40)
    - Project Publicity & Background (Box 40)
    - Boston, Musica Viva (Box 40)
    - Rhode Island State Council on the Arts (Box 40)
    - New Music Ensemble of Providence (Box 40)
    - N.E.A. Application & Award Letter, 1977 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, 1974 June-1975 June (Box 40)
    - Programming Ideas (Box 40)
    - Evaluation - Meeting & Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 40)
    - Sponsor Evaluation (Box 40)
    - Arthur Custer Article, Musical Quarterly, 1975 January (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, 1974 June (Box 40)
    - Budget, Payment & Fin. Rept., 1973-1974 (Box 40)
    - Sponsors - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 40)
    - Programs, Releases, 1973-1974 (Box 40)
    - N.E.A. Application & Award Letter, 1973-1974 (Box 40)
    - Reference, N.E.A. Sample Report (Box 40)
    - CCS, William Wallach and Will Welling, 1975 (Box 40)
    - Brochures (Box 40)
    - New England Contemporary Music Circuit pamphlets (Box 41)
    - Releases & Reviews, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Correspondence, circa 1975 July-1978 (Box 41)
    - Agreement brochure contract (Box 41)
    - Trinity College, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Report to N.E.A, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Westport, Friends of Music, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Mattatuck Community College, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Rhode Island College, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Manchester Community College, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Brown University, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Providence College, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - University of Rhode Island, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Northern Essex Community College, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Project I, Brown University, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Wooster Art Museum, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Smith College, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Cape Cod Community College, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Simon’s Rock College, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Massasoit Community College, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Book - Circuit, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Planning Meeting, 1976 February 25 (Box 41)
    - For Evaluation Session, 1976 January (Box 41)
    - Signed contracts, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
    - Report to N.E.A., 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Amherst College, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Barrington College, Rhode Island, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Wadsworth Athenaeum, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Providence College, Rhode Island, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Greenfield Community College, Massachusetts, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Ms. Porter’s School, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Fairfield University, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Clark Art Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Educational Center for Arts, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - University of Rhode Island, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Hillandale Barn Concert, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Housatonic Valley Regional High School, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Westerly Center for the Arts, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Manchester Community College, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Regis College, Massachusetts, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Hotchkiss School, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Massasoit Community College, Massachusetts, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Simons Rock College, Massachusetts, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Posters, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Photos of Performing Groups, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
    - Reviews, Comments, 1973-1974 (Box 41)
  - Capitol Concert Series, 1973-1977 (Box 42)
    - Connecticut Dance Theatre, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Promotion, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Ballet Etudes Rep. Co., 1975 (Box 42)
    - General, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Eastern Brass Quintet, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Manchester Pipes, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Payments, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Posters, 1975-1977 (Box 42)
    - General, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Paul Winter Consort, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Hartford Symphony Orchestra, 1973-1974 (Box 42)
    - Jacob’s Reunion, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Little Theatre of the Deaf, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Photographer, Michael Brett, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Rufus Rose, Puppeteer, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Producer’s Guild, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Norwalk Youth Symphony, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Artists Collective, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Greater Hartford Youth Chorale, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Ballet Etudes Rep. Co., 1973-1974 (Box 42)
    - Manchester Pipes, 1973-1974 (Box 42)
    - Planning Stage, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Piano Rental, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Publicity Distribution, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Budget, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Press Releases/News Articles, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Wesleyan African Drum Ensemble, 1973-1974 (Box 42)
    - Publicity flyers and posters, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Publicity/ Press Coverage, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Planning/arrangement forms, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Poster Designers, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Secretary of State, 1973 (Box 42)
    - New Haven Opera Society, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Photographer, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Legislative Management, 1973 (Box 42)
    - C.P.T.V., 1973 (Box 42)
    - Hartford Ballet Company, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Simsbury Light Opera Company, 1973-1974 (Box 42)
    - Hartford Symphony Orchestra, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Jean Redpath, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Little Theatre of the Death, 1973-1974 (Box 42)
    - Eastern Brass Quintet, 1973-1974 (Box 42)
    - Greater Hartford Youth Chorale, 1973-1974 (Box 42)
    - Artists Collective, 1973-1974 (Box 42)
    - Letters of Invitation Notification, 1973 (Box 42)
- Series 8. Arts Calendars, 1966-1978
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1966-1975 (Box 43)
  - 1966 February (Box 43)
  - 1966 October (Box 43)
  - 1966 September (Box 43)
  - 1966 April (Box 43)
  - 1966 March (Box 43)
  - 1966 December (Box 43)
  - 1966 May (Box 43)
  - 1966 October (Box 43)
  - 1967 December (Box 43)
  - 1967 May (Box 43)
  - 1967 October (Box 43)
  - 1967 April (Box 43)
  - 1966 November (Box 43)
  - 1966 July-August (Box 43)
  - 1967 January (Box 43)
  - 1967 February (Box 43)
  - 1967 September (Box 43)
  - 1967 June (Box 43)
  - 1968 September (Box 43)
  - 1968 October (Box 43)
  - 1968 November (Box 43)
  - 1968 December (Box 43)
    blue
  - 1968 December (Box 43)
    green
  - 1969 January (Box 43)
  - 1969 February (Box 43)
  - 1969 March (Box 43)
  - 1969 April (Box 43)
  - 1969 May-December (Box 43)
  - 1970 January-December (Box 43)
  - 1971 January-December (Box 43)
  - 1972 January (Box 43)
  - 1972 May (Box 43)
  - 1972 June (Box 43)
  - 1972 July-August (Box 43)
  - 1972 September (Box 43)
  - 1972 October (Box 43)
  - 1972 November (Box 43)
  - 1972 December (Box 43)
  - 1973 January-December (Box 43)
  - 1974 January (Box 43)
  - 1974 February (Box 43)
  - 1974 March (Box 43)
  - 1974 April (Box 43)
  - 1974 May (Box 43)
  - 1974 June (Box 43)
  - 1974 July-August (Box 43)
    newsprint
  - 1974 July-August (Box 43)
    regular
  - 1974 September (Box 43)
  - 1974 October (Box 43)
  - 1974 November (Box 43)
  - 1974 December (Box 43)
  - 1975 January-June (Box 43)
  - 1975 July-August (Box 43)
  - 1975 July-August (Box 43)
  - 1975 September-December (Box 43)
  - 1976 January (Box 44)
  - 1976 March (Box 44)
  - 1976 April (Box 44)
  - 1976 May (Box 44)
  - 1976 June (Box 44)
  - 1976 July-August (Box 44)
  - 1976 September-December (Box 44)
  - 1977 January-December (Box 44)
  - 1978 January-September (Box 44)
- Series 9. Environmental Awareness Project, 1969-1970
  - Connecticut Building Types- A Review of Influences and Patterns (4 copies), 1634-1920 (Box 45)
  - Part II - Narrative - the Community (Box 45)
  - Excerpt from the AIA Environmental Education Guidebook (Box 45)
  - Our Man- Made Environment-Book Seven (Box 45)
  - Our Man- Made Environment-Book Seven (Box 45)
  - Materials from “Gee” (Box 45)
  - Business for Beauty (Box 45)
  - Vital Questions - American Inst. of Architects (Box 45)
  - The New City: Architecture and Urban Renewal (Box 45)
  - Arts in General Education, 1969,1October (Box 45)
  - Man and His Environment, 1970 (Box 45)
  - Seymour, Connecticut - A Report on Visual Appearance, 1970 June 6 (Box 45)
  - Anarchy 97 - Architects and People (Box 45)
  - New Developments in Environmental Education, 1970 November 16 (Box 45)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings and letters (Box 45)
  - Original Copy - Letters of Support, Title III - Application Environmental Awareness (Box 45)
  - Paul V. Elsherry, Jr. (Box 45)
  - Steven Rosenthal (Box 45)
  - Harris Stone (Box 45)
  - Nancy Doernberg (Box 45)
  - Jane Knab (Box 45)
  - Susan Vogel (Box 45)
  - Interview - Environ. Awareness, September 21 (Box 45)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 45)
  - Middletown Application (Box 45)
  - Environmental Awareness Project (Box 45)
  - Environmental Awareness Educational Project (Box 45)
  - Environmental Awareness Curriculum Project (Box 45)
  - City of Middletown (Box 45)
  - Environmental Design Group (Box 45)
  - Richard C. Ellis (Box 45)
  - Norton Juster (Box 45)
  - Robert B. Clement, Jr. (Box 45)
  - Earl Pope (Box 45)
  - Arthur E. Hacker, Jr. (Box 45)
  - Harris B. Stone (Box 45)
  - 300 Years Critiques (Box 45)
  - Historic American Building Survey V (Box 45)
  - Historic Photographs Methods (Box 45)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 45)
  - Connecticut Architecture - Press (Box 45)
  - Development Commission (Box 45)
  - Department of Community Affairs (Box 45)
  - Elric Endersby (Box 45)
  - Anthony Schneider (Box 45)
  - Bills Paid (Box 45)
  - Bills Unpaid (Box 45)
  - Knox Foundation (Box 45)
  - In-Kind Services - Matching Funds (Box 45)
  - Funding Sources (Box 45)
  - Connecticut Historical Commission (Box 45)
  - 300 Years - Budget (Box 45)
  - Photographers and Designers (Box 45)
  - Labels for Pictures (Box 45)
  - 300 Years (Box 45)
  - Mr. Michael Croman (envelope) (Box 45)
  - Exhibit Material MP II (Box 45)
- Series 10. Internship Program, 1974-1976
  - Excerpts from Program Evaluation by the Intern (Box 46)
  - The Evaluation of the 74 Internship Program of the CCA by Thomas P. Murphy (Box 46)
  - The 1974 Arts Administration Internship Program - Guest Speakers (Box 46)
  - 1974 January (Box 46)
  - Interns, 1974 (Box 46)
  - Orientation, 1st Week, 1974 January 7-11 (Box 46)
  - Orientation, 2nd Week, 1974 January 14-18 (Box 46)
  - Orientation 3rd Week, 1974 January 21-25 (Box 46)
  - Ronald F. Coya (Box 46)
  - Orientation, 4th Week, 1974 January 28 - February 1 (Box 46)
  - 1974 February (Box 46)
  - Week Five, 1974 February 11-February 15 (Box 46)
  - Week Six, 1974 February 11-February 15 (Box 46)
  - Week Seven, 1974 February 18-February 22 (Box 46)
  - Weeks Eight, 1974 February 25-March 1 (Box 46)
  - 1974 March (Box 46)
  - Week Nine, 1974 March 4-8 (Box 46)
  - Week Ten, 1974 March 11-15 (Box 46)
  - Week Eleven, 1974 March 18-22 (Box 46)
  - A.C.A. New York City Conference, 1974 March 20 (Box 46)
  - Lincoln Center (Box 46)
  - 1974 April (Box 46)
  - Week Twelve, 1974 March 25-29 (Box 46)
  - Week Thirteen, 1974 April 1-5 (Box 46)
  - Week Fourteen, 1974 April 8-12 (Box 46)
    There are no items for this week.
  - Week Fifteen, 1974 April 15-19 (Box 46)
  - Week Sixteen, 1974 April 22-28 (Box 46)
  - A.C.A. Hartford Conference, 1974 April 26-28 (Box 46)
  - 1974 May (Box 46)
  - 1974 June (Box 46)
  - 1974 July-August (Box 46)
  - 1974 September-October (Box 46)
  - 1974 November-December (Box 46)
  - George W. Bentley, 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Annabelle Simon Cohn, 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Eric K. Hughes (Box 46)
  - Peter C. Oberlink (Box 46)
  - Eric Hughes (Box 46)
  - Kathleen Meagher (Box 46)
  - Kip Rosmarin (Box 46)
  - Carol Spitzer (Box 46)
- Series 11. Executive Director's Correspondence, 1966-1969
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - A - C (Box 47)
  - D - G (Box 47)
  - H - J (Box 47)
  - K - N (Box 47)
  - O - R (Box 48)
  - S (Box 48)
  - T - Z (Box 48)
- Series 12. News Clippings, 1962-1978
  - Newsclips, undated (Box 60)
  - Rescue, 1967-1969 (Box 60)
  - Music Programs Commission sponsor, 1967-1969 (Box 60)
  - Newsclips, 1967 (Box 60)
  - Theater of the Deaf, 1967 (Box 60)
  - Eugene O"Neill Theater, 1967 (Box 60)
  - Community Theater Workshop - Long Wharf Theater, 1967 September 16-17 (Box 60)
  - Project Create, 1967 June (Box 60)
  - Aid to Southbury Project, 1967 January (Box 60)
  - CUNO Foundation grant to Commission, 1967 January (Box 60)
  - Connecticut College Council for the Promotion of the Arts - Willimantic meeting, 1967 January (Box 60)
  - Editorial comment about the Commission, 1967-1969 (Box 60)
  - Windsor Arts Commission, 1967 January (Box 60)
  - January Commission meeting, 1967 January (Box 60)
  - Karl Heinz Stockhausen, 1967 January-February (Box 60)
  - Connecticut Capitol Center plan, 1967 March (Box 60)
  - Legislators' Jazz Band, 1967 March-June (Box 60)
  - Orchestra tours, 1967 March (Box 60)
  - Danbury City Cultural Commission, 1967 March (Box 60)
  - March Commission meeting, 1967 March (Box 60)
  - Commission appointments, Van Doren, Wolf, 1967 March (Box 60)
  - Solomons Gus, Jr. - Master Class, 1967 March-April (Box 60)
  - Eglevsky Ballet - Manchester, 1967 April (Box 60)
  - Danbury Scott-Fanton Museum, 1967 April (Box 60)
  - New Haven Festival of Arts, 1967 May (Box 60)
  - Torrington Arts Festival, 1967 June (Box 60)
  - Stratford Cultural Commission, 1967 June (Box 60)
  - New Haven Opera Society, 1967 (Box 60)
  - Project F-5 Museum Grant Program, 1967 February-March (Box 60)
  - Hearing for Connecticut symphony orchestras, 1967 February-March (Box 60)
  - Dance Teachers Workshop, Connecticut College for Women, New London, 1967 August 10-13 (Box 60)
  - New Haven Symphony Concert, Danbury, 1967 January-February (Box 60)
  - Community Theater Conference, 1966-1968 (Box 60)
  - Dance clippings, 1966-1970 (Box 60)
  - Wadsworth Athenaeum, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - Local arts councils, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - Project Create, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - Opera - Greater Hartford, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - Arts Festivals in Connecticut, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - Connecticut Arts Commission Calendar, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - Non-Commission sponsored programs, 1966-1968 (Box 60)
  - Coordinating Council on the Arts, 1966-1968 (Box 60)
  - Exhibits - Hartford, 1966 (Box 60)
  - General Music Info, 1966 (Box 60)
  - Opera - General, 1966 (Box 60)
  - Museums, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - General Arts Commission, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - Anthony Keller, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - Performances, exhibits, educational programs, Commission sponsored, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - Funds - Connecticut Commission, 1966-1969 (Box 60)
  - Films, 1966-1968 (Box 60)
  - 7C's, 1966-1968 (Box 60)
  - Painters, sculptors, performers, 1966-1968 (Box 60)
  - Theater events - Greater Hartford, 1966-1967 (Box 60)
  - Project F-8 Film Festival, 1966 September-October (Box 60)
  - Hartford State Company, 1966 (Box 60)
  - Out of state art events, 1966 (Box 60)
  - Martha Graham, 1966 (Box 60)
  - General interest, 1966 (Box 60)
  - News clips, 1966 (Box 60)
  - News clips, 1966 (Box 60)
  - Music events - Greater Hartford, 1966 (Box 60)
  - Hartt College, 1966 (Box 60)
  - Student Productions, 1966 (Box 60)
  - Connecticut Arts, 1966 (Box 60)
  - June Commission meeting, 1966 June (Box 60)
  - Commission awarded federal $45,000 grant, 1966 July (Box 60)
  - Goodspeed opening, 1966 July (Box 60)
  - Commission's Statewide Conference on the Arts, 1966 May-June (Box 60)
  - April Commission meeting, 1966 April (Box 60)
  - A.C.A. New York Conference, 1966 May (Box 60)
  - May Commission meeting, 1966 May (Box 60)
  - Tom Sawyer Project, 1966 December (Box 60)
  - Clinton Forum, 1966 December - 1967 January (Box 60)
  - Hartford Symphony Orchestra Concert - Danielson, 1967 January - February (Box 60)
  - Connecticut State Music Teachers Association meetings, 1966 September - 1967 February (Box 60)